[Music]
the whole organization is tipped upside
down if we really drew a pyramid
today and the pyramid was upside down
the agents are at the top of the pyramid
and Dave and I are at the bottom of the
pyramid and so everything that we do
everything that's here at the campus
everything that's done at the line level
is meant to serve agents that's an agent
Centric company there are four guiding
principles to the company commitment
accountability personal responsibility
and vision and we've always those have
always held Us in very good stead Mason
McDuffy has a long and Rich tradition
founded in 1887 by John Mason an
immigrant to the United States and
shortly after that in the turn of the
century he was joined by Duncan McDuffy
and they formed the partnership which
became known as Mason McDuffy realy and
so that rich history goes over some
almost 120 years now we describe
ourselves as a fullservice real estate
company so not only do we work with
buyers and sellers in finding the right
home for them and the family but
supporting them in the ancillary
Services which we refer to as our family
of services to complete the transaction
so we're involved in the mortgage
business we're involved in the home
protection business we currently have
some 5,000 agents within our network
over the next 5 years years we'll grow
this to 10,000 agents we're at 129
locations doing $14 billion worth of
business some 29,000 transactions we
have the best training um for new agents
and experienced agents alike in the
industry as a hes most of the new agents
that get a license give an exam which
has nothing to do with buying or selling
real estate here at credential they
train you for 2 weeks understanding
contracts and basically trying to get
you to jump start your business the
market changes constantly and we need to
keep ahead of the market and make sure
that our agents are are well trained to
adapt to the changes that are taking
place we offer training at all different
levels we offer training for brand new
agents coming in we offer them
technology training and we also offer
training that allows them to move
forward to the next level and and really
achieve their goals we have a large
Hispanic market and as such we provide
our agents with a certification program
uh training on an ongoing basis and
marketing materials in Spanish the
website is a critical tool to show the
brand and demonstrate the Forward
Thinking uh ideas of this company that's
Progressive it's going to be a brokerage
of the future it was an ambitious
release that has really brought the
experience closer to customers easy for
them to search homes easier for them to
save homes easier for them to get in
touch with what they're looking for and
also get in touch with our agents the
most important part of the real estate
trans transaction continues to be the
relationship between the agent and the
consumer technology is an enabler
technology allows the agent to be more
efficient in their dealings with the
consumer we need to continue to build
tools for our agents and um as such
we've just released a new webtop 5.0
platform which is a very very
comprehensive tool set for agents to
keep in touch with the consumers
electronically and there's a component
for the consumers as well to
to keep in touch with the properties
that they may be interested in looking
at and keeping in touch with the agents
that they're dealing with one thing
about this organization that's fantastic
is it's very clearly expressed and
articulated what our vision is where
we're going how we want to get there
this is how it affects you this is how
it will benefit you this is how you can
participate in it we've definitely got
the Work Hard Play Hard mentality uh we
have a great time it's definitely like
an extended family the Brokers of the
future in my mind is one that takes
great people and great technology and
delivers fantastic service to clients so
when clients think about they want to
buy or sell a home the first thing I
think about is credential California
realy it's an opportunity for you to
discover yourself discover how capable
you are of being successful there's
tremendous opportunity for growth in the
future and it really is an exciting time
in real estate if people want to be part
of building something great being part
of the best brokerage in America then
they should come here because that's the
kind of people are looking for
[Music]